the Jacob Rodriguez. What did you like
about him? I could see the excitement in
your face.
>> We're buzzing in there in the room. Um
Jacob's a guy we we've coveted for a
long time. You know, John talked about
good football players and bringing good
football players in here. Jacob's one of
those guys, a flag bearer, captain going
to walk in day one and be that type of
guy. Takes the ball away. Uh run game,
pass game, three down player. uh go down
the list of of every single attribute
that you want an inside backer. That's
what this guy is.
>> And when you look at uh the measurables
with him, what what what do you see?
>> I mean, he hits all the marks, you know,
he hits all the marks, you know, through
the evaluation process, obviously it
starts with the tape. Tape screams to
you a guy that's just a good football
player. He's physical. He's tough. um at
the inside linebacker position in
today's game, you want to see guys that
can play on third down. And obviously
with his production, um he proves that,
you know, he's a he's a blitzer, he's
coverage, it's it's forced fumbles, it's
PBUS, it's interceptions, he does it
all. Um and then on top of that, from a
skill set, you you throw in the
intangibles and it's through the roof.
Um like I said, this guy's a flag
bearer. Uh he's a captain. Um and we
expect in short order he's going to do
the same thing here. and he's one of
those guys going to earn the respect uh
pretty quickly.
>> Does he have special teams abilities?
>> Yeah, absolutely. Absolutely. Guys in
that position, you you're always looking
for guys that, you know, that has his
attributes because he can run uh he
could play in space like we talked about
third down value. All those things kind
of translate well to the to the kicking
game.
>> When uh Sully and half have talked about
competition here, you've got Jordan
Brooks, you've got Terrell Dodson,
this competition. Yeah, 100% every guy
we bring in, you know, no different than
the guys we brought in last night. You
know what I mean? They're going to come
in here and compete. Um, that's going to
be the culture that's created here. Um,
you know, and this guy won't back down
from anything.
>> What did you guys learn from him at the
senior bowl when he had a big week out
there at Mobile?
>> Yeah, just another another uh, you know,
test, you know, and that he passed. Um,
I think like we we were talking about, I
think Sully's hit on it. you know,
there's always different markers that
you go through through the process,
analytics and, you know, combine and
measurables and tape and, you know, meet
with the coaches, you know, the mental
part of the game, which is exceptional
with this kid. Um, and senior bowl, it
just kind of proves another stepping
stone of like, hey, you know, this
dude's a guy, he's going to go, there's
clarity uh that comes and uh he passed
every test. When you talk about
leadership, uh, that Tech defense has
some good players, Lee Hunter and Romelo
Height. And where did you see Jacob's
leadership in that game?
>> Yeah, I mean that that's one of the
things that I think sticks out with this
kid is, you know, on a team with really
good players. They've done a tremendous
job there at Texas Tech bringing in
talent and, you know, this guy sticks
out in terms of of like we talk I keep
saying flag bearer, but I mean that's
what he was there. You know what I mean?
and and he's been that for a couple of
years. And uh anybody that you talk to
at that school call and and our scouts,
that's one of the first things out of
their mouth is is just the type of
leadership and the character uh makeup
that this kid has.
>> I understand he has a lot of ball
production, interceptions, forced
fumbles. How does he go about
accomplishing that?
>> In every single way. I mean, there's
there's not really a a thing on tape,
you know, from a statline that I don't
think he hasn't done, you know. uh, you
know, punch outs and, you know, like we
said, PBUS in the past game,
interceptions in the past game. He's got
a unique uh, spatial awareness, ability
to play in space. Um, feeling, you know,
where his zones are and where where
bodies are from the other team. Um, and
he closes them down in a hurry. So, he's
got a he's got a unique anticipatory
skill uh, that that helps him in the
pass game. I think he's like a he's a
converted at quarterback, tight end,
just I I know Tech gave him some
touches.
>> Football playing Jesse. That's what he
is, you know, and and it doesn't matter
where they put him, he makes plays and
he found a home obviously at inside
backer.
>> I know Tech gave him some touches to
boost those Heisman Humbers. Is there a
future package coming? Do you see him
doing
>> Yeah, I don't know. You saw Proctor,
too. He got the ball, too. So, between
him and uh Rodriguez, you know, I'm sure
I'm sure Bobby can come up with
something.
>> How much quarter?
Yeah, my bad. Jokes aside, his his
history as a quarterback, how do you see
that translate to him on defense? How do
you how does that impact how he plays?
>> Yeah, I think it just sees the game, you
know, whenever you get guys like that.
Um, you see it sometimes safeties, you
know, similar when they played wide out
and uh you see the game from the other
side of the ball and I think from a
quarterback perspective, you're learning
what the defense is doing to, you know
what I mean, to uh affect you and then
you understand what you're trying to do
to affect the defense. Now you flip it
around and he knows automatically when
guys are, you know, going quarterback's
going through reads and where your eyes
are and um so he affects the game that
way. He kind of see and you you feel it
in his tape. It looks like he's not
running sometimes because he's already
there. He's a step ahead. Um and that's
that's going to take time at our level.
The game is a different game, different
speed. Um but I think in short order,
you know, he's going to figure that out
pretty quick.
>> When you talk about intangibles and
unique things, uh you know, his wife is
a is a pilot. Are are there other things
about him that are unique of the
>> hell of a mustache? You know, he got
hell of a mustache. But no, I you know,
I think, you know, I just like I said
earlier, I think it's just what makes
him unique is in today's day and age,
you know, guys that that work that we
it's the things we covet, you know, guys
that are selfish, that are that are, you
know, competitive, that are all about
ball, good human beings, good people, um
good teammates, you know, all the things
that we're stress. He's about everything
that we want to be about and what we
want to build here. So, um, you know, we
can't tell you how fired up we are about
this one.
>> How excited were you to find out that
the athletic profile at the combine kind
of matched like the good tape because he
had really good numbers kind of across
the board.
>> Yeah, I think that's that's always part
of it, you know, and and and those
things, you know, you put you got to put
stock in it. You know, this is a this
league is about guys with traits and um,
you know, so that's definitely one of
the the measuring points. We don't put
you we put value in it. It's not it
doesn't kill you, you know, but it just
tells you when you got to buy things,
you know, and and you know, when it came
to his his measurables and and testing
numbers, you watch him at the count, you
watch him move live and how he sinks and
bends and um it it kind of matches up
and marries up to the, you know, third
down value that we thought he had.
>> Can you tell us what you like about
Caleb?
>> Yeah, Caleb uh obviously brings uh some
size to the room, right? um good
athlete, can run the full route tree. Um
he's uh he's got some dynamic traits. Uh
saw him at the Senior Bowl obviously in
the combine. Had good workouts there. Uh
big catch radius. Uh can really get
outside of his frame, competitive kid,
great makeup. Um yeah, so really really
enjoyed getting to know him through the
process. Um yeah, and we've you know
vetted him from from Florida. He started
his career at Florida. um you know, high
marks across the board all four years in
college. So,
>> what is it about Texas Tech Red Raiders
that you guys really liked?
>> Yeah, it seems seems to be working out
for us, right? Um there's been a few
good players here from Tech over over
the years. So, you know, from Jack, Zack
to uh Jake and obviously Jordan right
now. Jordan's pretty excited. He's he's
been in the building a few times already
uh tonight in and out of the draft room.
So, it's uh it's it's been good. So you
I guess you gota keep going back to
where you found him, right? So
>> how does uh how does Caleb fit in? You
know, there's a a I guess a physicality
uh theme going on here and and uh
aggression and things like that. How
does Caleb fit in with with with that uh
I guess that mold?
>> Sure. Um you know, we're obviously just
looking for the best players available.
Um, and he obviously brings size and
athletic ability and the he's got the uh
the movement skills to uh to to do
everything we want in terms of the of
what we're asking the wide receiver
position to do. So, um there's really
nothing specific there as we just build
out this this wide receiver room. Um you
know, he kind of checks just a lot of
boxes for us.
>> Does he have special teams
possibilities?
>> Absolutely. Yeah. Yeah. With his size
and speed and length, um there's that's
always on the table. Was the size and
length a priority for this wide receiver
pick?
>> Uh, not not necessarily. It just
happened to fit kind of where we were in
the draft. So,